ILGWU Local 23-25 Records 5780/059
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 23-25 News Summary, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- " A Record of Progress"; Reports from Local 23-25, 1965-1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- "Development of Periphery Forms of Organization: Some Lessons from new York Garment Industry", 1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  By Florence Palpacuer
- "On the Move: A Report on Gains Made During the Years 1971 to 1974 And Plans for the Future" (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Scrapbook; newspaper clippings; flyers; photos
- "Moving Forward Together: Report on Local 23's Progress", 1959-1962 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Publicity on Immigration Project, 1982-1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Immigration Project Logbook; Cuban/Haitian, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Local 23-25 Membership Survey, 1981-1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Benefits (staff), 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Immigration Testimony and Resolutions, 1980-1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Immigration Project Statistics, 1987-1994 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Immigration Reform and Control Act/Immigration and Naturalization Service Cooperation Agreement, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Negotiations (press), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Negotiations (press), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Immigration Project, 1986-1991 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Immigration Project, 1986-1990 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Immigration Project: Report to the GEB, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Immigration Project; Recognized Organizations, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Immigration Project; Immigration Cases, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Immigration Project; Seminar on Immigration Law, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Directory of Project Made by ILGWU Members (Box 24, Folder 16)
  Union Label Department
- Council for American Fashion Fund; Shimon Cohen Expenses, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Council for American Fashions Fund; Articles of Association and Bylaws, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Reception for Winner, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Reception for Winners, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Eng, Don Yi, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Mino, Mercedes, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Diaz, Maria, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Au Yeung, Mei-Yin; Parsippany HS (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Chan, Joan Kawi-Fan; Washington Irving, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Chan, Hoi (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Hoi, Chan; Aviation HS, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Coella, Hereilia; George Washington HS, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Scholarship Reports, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Scholarship Reports, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Scholarship Report, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Scholarship Report - Midyear Report, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Mid-Year Report, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Scholarship Recipients, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Scholarships, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Scholarships, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Reception for Winners - Invitations, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Reception for Winners Program, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Scholarship Cost, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Reception for Winners, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Scholarship Formal Notices, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Cover Letters and Questionnaires for Textbook Scholarship (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Mailing Listing for Textbook Scholarship Program, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Scholarship Recipients Checklist, 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Mailing Listing for Textbook Scholarship, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Scholarship Files (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Selection Committee Correspondence, 1984;1986 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Selection Committee, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- UFT College Scholarship Fund (Box 25, Folder 31)
- College Financial Aid Emergency (Box 25, Folder 32)
- AFL-CIO Department of Education Scholarship Guidelines (Box 25, Folder 33)
- College Textbook Scholarships (Box 25, Folder 34)
- CSS Correspondence and Forms (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Redesign Forms, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Redesign Forms, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Scholarship Recipients, 1981-1986 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Scholarship Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Scholarship Mailings and Receipts (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Scholarship Ceremony (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Scholarship Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Selection Committee Correspondence, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- [No Tite], 1984 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  Chinese
- Press and Publicity, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Press and Publicity, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Press and Publicity, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Press and Publicity, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- Scholarship Program, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 49)
- Application Letters, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- Scholarship Letter Application, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- Application Letters, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- Scholarship Applicant Mailing List, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- Cover Letter to 1985 Fourth Year Recipients and Questionnaires (Box 25, Folder 54)
- ILGWU National Scholarship (Box 25, Folder 55)
- Formal Notices, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 56)
- Formal Notices, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 57)
- Formal Notices, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 58)
- Formal Notices, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 59)
- Application Letters, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 60)
- Scholarship News Pictures (Box 25, Folder 61)
- Publicity Mailing List (Box 25, Folder 62)
- Mailing List (Box 25, Folder 63)
- Scholarship Documents, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 64)
- The Student Council, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  Brochures; Spanish Included
- Student Magazine Entries. Chinatown, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Culture Week (Box 26, Folder 3)
  Programs, Brochures and Schedule
- Project Cultural Celebration. Chinatown, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Teachers' Meeting. Pulling Out Grammar From Text (Box 26, Folder 5)
  January 26th; Chinatown
- Small Groups Curriculum. Chinatown, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Worker-Family Education Program. Teachers' Meetings & Lectures, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Para-Professional, Staff Development Meetings & Worker-Family Education Program, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- A Few 'Rule of Thumb' Numbers and Organizations & Testimony of Jay Mazur, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  Readings
- Election Day Resource Packet & Other Resources, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Student List, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Unite! Certificates of Achievement, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- HS Fashion ESL Teachers, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Silver Palace Workers, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  Newspaper Clippings Included; Chinese Included
- ILGWU & UNITE Immigration Project Staff List and Documents, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  Chinese Included
- Asian-American Magazines, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- SACTWU Convention & Speech Draft, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- College Textbook Scholarship Guest List & Program Operation, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  July 23
- College Textbook Scholarship Program & Applicants List, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Correspondence, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Scholarship Follow-up, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Publicity Recipients Rejection Correspondence, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Award Ceremony, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  Letter to Parent, Student, Press and Program Sheet
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Scholarship Report, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Scholarship Selection Committee, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Scholarship Award Ceremony, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  Chinese Newspaper Clipping Included
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Winners & Recipients, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  Chinese Included; Chinese News Clipping Included
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Fourth Year Recipients, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Scholarship Renewal Problem Case, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Scholarship Selection Committee, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Scholarship Program Correspondence, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Scholarships Presentation, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Information Sheet, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Local 23-25. Lana Cheung Newspaper Clippings, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Office Forms (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Local 23-25 Members Census, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Benefit Fund Collections, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Local 23-25 ILGWU Resolutions & Contributions, 1991-1995 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Nominations Meeting, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  February 22
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Day Care Regulations, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Local 23-25 College Textbook Scholarship Program Fourth Year Recipients Questionnaire, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  September 6
- Local 23-25 College Textbook Scholarship Program Fourth Year Recipients Questionnaire, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- Local 23-25 College Textbook Scholarship Program Fourth Year Recipients Questionnaire, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- Jobbers. Shop Investigations, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown [Folder 1 of 2], 1995 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown [Folder 2 of 2], 1995 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- GIDC Information, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- Last Issue of Justice and Labor Unity. Unite Convention Issue, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  Newspaper Clippings Included; Summer
- Shop Representatives Committee, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  Chinese, Spanish and English Included
- Election and Objection Committee (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Election and Objection Committee. Executive Board Members (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Nomination Meeting Agenda, 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  February 22, 1995 2c; January 22,1992 1c
- United Administration Group of Local 23-25 ILGWU. Agenda, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- United Administration Group Elections, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- United Administration Group of Local 23-25 Nominations Meeting & Speeches, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- United Administration Group Nominations. Meeting, Speeches and Minutes, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Local 23-25 College Textbook Scholarship Program, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Local 23-25 College Textbook Scholarship Program Essays and Forms, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Scholarship Student Aid, 1988-1991 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Local 23-25 College Textbook Scholarship Program. Publicity, Press & Scholarships, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  Chinese Included; Local 23-25 1991 News Included
- The 1991 Textbook Scholarship Selection Committee (Box 27, Folder 13)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Correspondence, Congratulation & Forms, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program Award Ceremony, 1991-1996 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  Chinese Included; Newspaper Clippings Included
- Scholarship Selection Committee, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  Photographs Included
- Textbook Scholarship Award Ceremony, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Renewal File, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Scholarship Program Publicity, Press, Letters & Information Booklets, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  Chinese Local 23-25 News Included 1c
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Correspondence, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Local 23-25 Scholarship Program Publicity, Press, Union Newspaper & High School Advisor Letter, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Scholarship Award Ceremony, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  Chinese Included; Local 23-25 News Included, English 1c, Chinese 1c
- AFL-CIO Scholarship Program, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program Selection Committee, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Renewal Scholarships, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Miscellaneous Letters, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program. Miscellaneous Letters, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- College Textbook Scholarship Program Award Ceremony, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  Chinese Newspaper Included; Local 23-25 News Included 1c
- Chung Pak Day Center, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- ILGWU Religious Chorus Songs. Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Program for the Baptist Home, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  August 8
- Program With Selected Songs (Box 27, Folder 33)
- ILGWU Song Book Cover Illustration (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Health and Welfare Local 23-25 ILGWU, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  Blouse, Skirt and Sportswear Workers' Union
- Executive Board Notes, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Tape Cassette Included
- Executive Board Meeting. Nomination Meeting. Election & Objection Committee Meeting, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Executive Board Local 23-25 Committee Meeting Agenda, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Executive Board Nomination Meeting Agenda, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Executive Board United Administration Group Election, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Executive Board Election & Objection Committee, 1986/1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Committees List & Donation Thank Yous, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Minutes of Meeting of the Election & Objection Committee, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  January 29
- 41st ILGWU Convention Agenda, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- United Administration Group Nominations Agenda, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Nomination Meeting Agenda and Speeches, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Executive Board Recommendations, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- UAG Convention Schedule of Per Diem, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Executive Board Election & Objection Committee Nominated Positions, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Executive Board Meeting Agenda & Attendance, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Executive Board Committees, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- United Administration Group Executive Committee Officers, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Executive Board Committee Members & Staff, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Executive Board Recommendations, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Executive Board Election and Convention Records, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- UAG Executive Committee Agenda, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  January 18
- Triennial Elections and Calendar of UAG, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Local 23-25 Nomination Meeting, Calendar and Agenda for Election, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Mobilizing Members for June 18 Rally. Executive Board Meeting Agenda & Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Minutes of Meeting of the Election & Objection Committee, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  March 2
- Executive Board Meeting. Agenda, Attendance, and Minutes, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  December 19
- Local 23-25 Executive Board Agenda, Meeting & Notes, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  August 20 & September 19; Two Tape Cassettes Included
- Chinese ILGWU Members for Justice, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  News Clipping Included; Chinese Included
- United Administration Group Meetings & Agenda, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Local 23-25 Executive Board Members Payment List, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Election And Objection Committee Nomination Applications, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- United Administration Group Election, 1989/1992 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  Calendar, UAG Executive Committee, Letter from UAG, UAG Agenda, Executive UAG Agenda, Letter to Executive Board
- Executive Board Committee Convention Records, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Local Executive Board Minutes & Agenda [Folder 1 of 2], 1989-1993 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Local Executive Board Minutes & Agenda [Folder 2 of 2], 1989-1993 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Minutes of the Executive Board Meetings, 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  Hardcover Book
- 5/11/90 - Executive Board, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  pulled from box 28, folder 1
- 9/19/96 Meeting of Executive Board (Box 30, Folder 1)
  pulled from box 28, folder 27
- 5/28/96, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 1)